Von Ezekiel Manaois

von.manaois@amail.com | +1 416 949 0639 www.linkedin.com/in/von-manaois-IT

Summary

Highly motivated and dedicated full-time student seeking employment opportunities to utilize my skills and gain practical experience here in Canada. With three years of work experience and a strong academic background, I am eager to contribute to a dynamic organization while further developing my professional skills.

GENERAL SKILLS

Communication
Problem Solving
Time Management
Teamwork
Adaptability
Customer Service

LANGUAGE

English Filipino

EDUCATION

Centennial College, May 2023 - Present Software Engineering Technology

Saint Louis University, Baguio City, Philippines, 2019 Bachelor of Science in Information Technology

REFERENCE

Patricia Joson 437-259-8655
Value Village anglubenp@gmail.com
Christine Perico 437-331-2631
Costco Wholesale Yabutchristine@yahoo.com

WORK EXPERIENCE

Company: Texas Instruments TIPI [Project Engineer at Wipro Limited]

2nd Position (Promoted): Real Time Dispatch and Line Management Level 2 <u>April 2022 – September 2022</u> **Job Description:**

- Investigate issues encountered in RTD and look for documented solutions
- Handling Account and Password change for database servers
- Extracting report using queries for RTD monitoring
- Manipulates data in the database as per user's request. (DML)
- Testing database connection
- Monitoring critical and non-critical alerts and processes
- Responds to email and probe for clarification of the request.
- Enable/disable running processes using unix
- Editing and updating files using text editor (vi)
- Provide technical solutions to wide range of problems and user request through the established system

1st Position: IT Operations Helpdesk [Asia Regional Helpdesk] / Dallas Automation Operations Support (September 2019 - March 2022)

Description: 1st Level IT support in Texas Instruments handling issues and concerns of its company's employees. Determine urgency of each request received and strictly follow escalation processes provided. Escalate issues or concerns to the proper support and issues that need coordination with Level 2 or Level 3 support groups.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Hardware

Assembly, Maintenance, Peripherals, Rebooting System, Printers and Scanners.

Software

Remote Desktop (VNC/Anydesk), Software Installation, Microsoft Office Standard, Oracle SQL, Adobe Creative Suite, WordPress, Photo and Video Editing. Canva

Networks

Network Configuration, Routers, Web Servers, LAN Technology. SSH

Programming Languages

HTML, CSS, SQL